HERE Publications 6199 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 9, Folder: 10 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 42: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: April-May
  - Item 43: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 44: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 45: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 46: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 47: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 48: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: May-June; Vol. 3, No. 5-6
  - Item 49: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: March-April; Vol.3 No. 3-4
  - Item 50: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: January-February; Vol. 3 No. 1-2
  - Item 51: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: November-December; Vol. 2 No. 9-10
  - Item 52: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: September-October; Vol. 2 No. 7-8
  - Item 53: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: August; Vol. 2 No. 6
  - Item 54: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: May; Vol. 2 No. 5
  - Item 55: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: April; Vol. 2 No. 4
  - Item 56: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: March; Vol. 2 No. 3
  - Item 57: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: February; Vol. 2 No. 2
  - Item 58: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: January; Vol. 2 No. 1
  - Item 59: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: December; Vol. 1 No. 3
  - Item 60: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: October-November; Vol. 1 No. 2
  - Item 61: Food for Thought - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: September; Vol. 1 No. 1
- Box: 10, Folder: 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 44
- Box: 10, Folder: 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 45
- Box: 10, Folder: 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 46
- Box: 10, Folder: 4 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 47
- Box: 10, Folder: 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 48
- Box: 10, Folder: 6 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 49
- Box: 10, Folder: 7 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 50
- Box: 10, Folder: 8 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 51
- Box: 10, Folder: 9 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 52
- Box: 10, Folder: 10 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 53
- Box: 10, Folder: 11 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 54
- Box: 11, Folder: 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 55
- Box: 11, Folder: 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 56
- Box: 11, Folder: 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 57
- Box: 11, Folder: 4 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 58
- Box: 11, Folder: 5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 59
- Box: 11, Folder: 6 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 60
- Box: 11, Folder: 7 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 61
- Box: 11, Folder: 8 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 62
- Box: 11, Folder: 9 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 63
- Box: 11, Folder: 10 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 64
- Box: 11, Folder: 11 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 64; Copy 2
- Box: 11, Folder: 12 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Notes: Vol. 65
- Box: 11, Folder: 13 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Notes: Vol. 66
- Box: 11, Folder: 14 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Notes: Vol. 67
- Box: 12, Folder: 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 68
- Box: 12, Folder: 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 69
- Box: 12, Folder: 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 70
- Box: 12, Folder: 4 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 71
- Box: 12, Folder: 5 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 72
- Box: 12, Folder: 6 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 73
- Box: 12, Folder: 7 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 74
- Box: 12, Folder: 8 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 75
- Box: 12, Folder: 9 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 76
- Box: 12, Folder: 10 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 77
- Box: 12, Folder: 11 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 78
- Box: 12, Folder: 12 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Notes: Vol. 79
- Box: 12, Folder: 13 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Notes: Vol. 80
- Box: 12, Folder: 14 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Notes: Vol. 81
- Box: 13, Folder: 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 82
- Box: 13, Folder: 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 83
- Box: 13, Folder: 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 84
- Box: 13, Folder: 4 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 85
- Box: 13, Folder: 5 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 86
- Box: 13, Folder: 6 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 87
- Box: 13, Folder: 7 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 88
- Box: 13, Folder: 8 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 89
- Box: 13, Folder: 9 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 90
- Box: 13, Folder: 10 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 91
- Box: 13, Folder: 11 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 92
- Box: 13, Folder: 12 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Notes: Vol. 92; Copy 2
- Box: 13, Folder: 13 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Notes: Vol. 93
- Box: 13, Folder: 14 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Notes: Vol. 94
- Box: 14, Folder: 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 95
- Box: 14, Folder: 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 96
- Box: 14, Folder: 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 97
- Box: 14, Folder: 4 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 98
- Box: 14, Folder: 5 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 99
- Box: 14, Folder: 6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 100
- Box: 14, Folder: 7 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 101
- Box: 14, Folder: 8 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 102
- Box: 14, Folder: 9 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Official Journal of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 103
- Box: 14, Folder: 10 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Union house, Union Bar: The History of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Author: Matthew Josephson
- Box: 14, Folder: 11 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Union house, Union Bar: The History of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Notes: Copy 2
- Box: 14, Folder: 12 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Union house, Union Bar: The History of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Notes: Copy 3
- Box: 14, Folder: 13 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Growth of a Union: The Life and Times of Edward Flore, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Author: Jay Rubin and M. J. Obermeier
- Box: 14, Folder: 14 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Fifty Years of Progress: A Brief History of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Fifty Years of Progress: A Brief History of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: 20th Anniversary of the Hotel and Restaurant Workers Union - Local 16, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Box: 14, Folder: 15 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: 100 Years of Service: A History of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: 100 Years of Service: A History of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: 100 Years of Service: A History of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Box: 14, Folder: 16 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Cook's Training Program (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Author: Cooks and Pastry Cooks Union Local #88
- Box: 14, Folder: 17 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Total Materials' Cost Cook's Training Program, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Total Materials' Cost Cook's Training Program, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Box: 14, Folder: 18 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Voice of Local 237: Official Monthly Bullentin, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Author: Hotal and Restaurant Employees Alliance, Local 237
    Notes: Volume 2; Semptember 26
- Box: 14, Folder: 19 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) Wall Calender, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Box: 15, Folder: 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Restaurant Agreement, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Author: Greater Chicago Area Local Joint Executive Board - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union
- Box: 15, Folder: 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Manual of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: Ritual, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union
    Notes: December 1
- Box: 15, Folder: 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Synopsis of Decisions of the General President of the Hotel and Restaurant Employes' International Alliance and Bartender's International League of America, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Author: General President Edward Flore
    Notes: January 1
- Box: 15, Folder: 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Manual for Organizing Civilian Employees of Nonappropriated Fund Instrumentalities on Federal Military Installations, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: Folder [1 of 4]
- Box: 15, Folder: 5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Manual for Organizing Civilian Employees of Nonappropriated Fund Instrumentalities on Federal Military Installations, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Notes: Folder [2 of 4]
- Box: 15, Folder: 6 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Manual for Organizing Civilian Employees of Nonappropriated Fund Instrumentalities on Federal Military Installations, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Notes: Folder [3 of 4]
- Box: 15, Folder: 7 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Manual for Organizing Civilian Employees of Nonappropriated Fund Instrumentalities on Federal Military Installations, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Notes: Folder [4 of 4]
- Box: 15, Folder: 8 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Role of John W. Wilhelm, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Author: Indian Gaming and the National Gambling Impact Study Commission